<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Card News Making Tool</string>
    <string name="title_activity_photo_editor">PhotoEditorActivity</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="upload_dialog_title">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="upload_picker_title">Select Picture</string>
    <string name="directory_create_fail">Failed to create directory</string>
    <string name="access_media_permissions_msg">To attach photos, we need to access media on your device</string>
    <string name="continue_txt">Continue</string>
    <string name="not_now">NOT NOW</string>
    <string name="media_access_denied_msg">You denied storage access, no photos will be added.</string>

    <string name="ic_close">"\ue918"</string>
    <string name="ic_text">"\ue945"</string>
    <string name="ic_draw">""\ue944</string>
    <string name="ic_images">"\ue949"</string>
    <string name="ic_save">"\ue946"</string>
    <string name="ic_clear_all">"\ue947"</string>
    <string name="ic_continue">"\ue948"</string>
    <string name="ic_delete">"\ue92c"</string>
    <string name="choose_from_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="choose_from_camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="erase">Erase</string>

    <string name="mylicense">
        LICENSE&#10;
        &#10;
        Software : Card_News_Making_Tool&#10;
        Team : Navigation&#10;
        &#10;
        This guarantee Card_News_Making_Tool License.&#10;
        * MIT License&#10;
        * CC 3.0 License&#10;
        &#10;
        Card_News_Making_Tool License is MIT License.&#10;
        &#10;
        2017.11.23&#10;
        Navigation&#10;
        &#10;
        &#10;
    </string>

    <string name="license">
        MIT License&#10;
        &#10;
        Copyright (c) 2017 Eventtus&#10;
        &#10;
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
        of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
        in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
        to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
        copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
        furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
        &#10;
        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
        copies or substantial portions of the Software.
        &#10;
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
        AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
        SOFTWARE.
        &#10;
        &#10;
        CC 3.0 License&#10;
        &#10;
        This work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License.&#10;
        To view a copy of this license, visit http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/ or
        send a letter to Creative Commons, PO Box 1866, Mountain View, CA 94042, USA.</string>
</resources>
</resources>
